talkbiznow.com 2013-06-30

# Talkbiznow - Business services for the business community

**Last Updated: 18th August 2008**

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

  * We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes
  * We will never share your contact information with another user, without your consent.
  * Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates, to the website, to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the Talkbiznow service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours does Talkbiznow collect.
  * How the information is used.
  * With whom the information may be shared.
  * How you can access and change your Account information.
  * What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by Talkbiznow.

How to contact us.  
**  
Information Collection**

_Registration_

In order to become a Talkbiznow user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, a brief summary of your professional background (current occupation & networking objectives), and choose a password.

_Profile Information_

Once a user, you may provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, professional experiences, and networking objectives. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities in the Talkbiznow system.

_Information about your Contacts_

In order to invite others to connect with you directly in Talkbiznow, you will enter their names and email addresses. This information will be used by Talkbiznow to send your invitation including a message that you write. The names and email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation and reminders.

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contacts into the private “My Contacts” section of our website. All information entered there will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the Talkbiznow network without your permission.  
All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

_Cookies & Log Files_

Like most web sites, Talkbiznow uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer, which allows Talkbiznow to recognise you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customise your experience on the web site.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your Talkbiznow account. The next time you visit the Talkbiznow web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognise you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information, however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the Talkbiznow site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Talkbiznow site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Talkbiznow web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Talkbiznow. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyse overall trends to help us improve the Talkbiznow service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third parties without your permission or except when required by law.

_Children_

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

**Information Use**

Talkbiznow is an online service dedicated to helping all types of professionals more effectively connect with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. 

_Talkbiznow Communications_

Talkbiznow will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Talkbiznow related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. Talkbiznow may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to [customerservice@talkbiznow.com](mailto:customerservice@talkbiznow.com).

_Customised Content_

Information you provide at registration or in your Profile section is also used to customise your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new users who have recently joined your network.

**Information Sharing**

_Sharing Information With Third Parties_

Talkbiznow takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. product managers, managing directors), industry, and geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email customer service.

_Partnering with Other Organisations to Offer Combined Services_

Talkbiznow partners with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services it will be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from Talkbiznow to the partner if you choose to use the combined service.

_Communications Between Users_

Many emails you initiate through Talkbiznow, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network), but will never list the people to whom you’re directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the Talkbiznow website, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.

_Legal Disclaimer_

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Talkbiznow account, at any time by logging in to your account on the Talkbiznow website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the Talkbiznow website. If you close your Talkbiznow account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Talkbiznow Privacy Policy that you have previously agree to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Talkbiznow service, please send your request to customerservice@talkbiznow.com. Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Talkbiznow under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to [customerservice@talkbiznow.com](mailto:customerservice@talkbiznow.com) within twenty business days of our receiving it.

**Security**

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on Talkbiznow is password-protected, and sensitive data is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and our web site. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Talkbiznow may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Questions or Comments**

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [customerservice@talkbiznow.com](mailto:customerservice@talkbiznow.com) or contact us at:

Customer Service Department, Talkbiznow Ltd., 2 Sheraton Street, London, W1F 8BH
